[
  {
    "index": 1,
    "Question": "甘い",
    "Answer": "sweet",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "Question": "酸っぱい",
    "Answer": "sour",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "Question": "苦い",
    "Answer": "bitter",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "Question": "塩辛い",
    "Answer": "salty",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "Question": "辛い",
    "Answer": "spicy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "Question": "渋い",
    "Answer": "astringent",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "Question": "まろやか",
    "Answer": "mellow",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "Question": "さっぱり",
    "Answer": "refreshing",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "Question": "濃厚",
    "Answer": "rich",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 10,
    "Question": "淡白",
    "Answer": "bland",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 11,
    "Question": "香ばしい",
    "Answer": "fragrant",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 12,
    "Question": "焦げた",
    "Answer": "charred",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 13,
    "Question": "焼きたて",
    "Answer": "freshly baked",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 14,
    "Question": "冷たい",
    "Answer": "cold",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 15,
    "Question": "熱い",
    "Answer": "hot",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 16,
    "Question": "温かい",
    "Answer": "warm",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 17,
    "Question": "ぬるい",
    "Answer": "lukewarm",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 18,
    "Question": "とろとろ",
    "Answer": "gooey",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 19,
    "Question": "ねばねば",
    "Answer": "sticky",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 20,
    "Question": "パリパリ",
    "Answer": "crispy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 21,
    "Question": "サクサク",
    "Answer": "crunchy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 22,
    "Question": "もちもち",
    "Answer": "chewy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 23,
    "Question": "ふわふわ",
    "Answer": "fluffy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 24,
    "Question": "ジューシー",
    "Answer": "juicy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 25,
    "Question": "シャキシャキ",
    "Answer": "crisp",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 26,
    "Question": "カリカリ",
    "Answer": "crackly",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 27,
    "Question": "しっとり",
    "Answer": "moist",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 28,
    "Question": "ざらざら",
    "Answer": "grainy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 29,
    "Question": "なめらか",
    "Answer": "smooth",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 30,
    "Question": "つるつる",
    "Answer": "slippery",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 31,
    "Question": "ほろほろ",
    "Answer": "crumbly",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 32,
    "Question": "ぷりぷり",
    "Answer": "springy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 33,
    "Question": "こってり",
    "Answer": "heavy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 34,
    "Question": "あっさり",
    "Answer": "light",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 35,
    "Question": "濃い",
    "Answer": "strong",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 36,
    "Question": "薄い",
    "Answer": "weak",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 37,
    "Question": "酸味がある",
    "Answer": "tangy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 38,
    "Question": "辛口",
    "Answer": "hot (spicy)",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 39,
    "Question": "甘口",
    "Answer": "mild (sweet)",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 40,
    "Question": "脂っこい",
    "Answer": "greasy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 41,
    "Question": "爽やか",
    "Answer": "refreshing",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 42,
    "Question": "香りが高い",
    "Answer": "aromatic",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 43,
    "Question": "芳醇",
    "Answer": "rich-flavored",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 44,
    "Question": "コクがある",
    "Answer": "full-bodied",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 45,
    "Question": "さくさく",
    "Answer": "flaky",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  },
  {
    "index": 46,
    "Question": "もちもち",
    "Answer": "chewy",
    "good": 0,
    "bad": 0
  }
]